thekicker.com 2016-03-17

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Welcome to Aboveaverage.com, brought to you by [Above Average Productions, Inc.](http://www.aboveaverage.com/), the digital comedy network from the [Broadway Video](http://www.broadwayvideo.com/) family (makers of Saturday Night Live, The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon, Late Night with Seth Meyers, Portlandia, and 30 Rock.)

Here at Above Average, we recognize visitors to aboveaverage.com or other web sites owned or operated by Above Average (the “Above Average websites“) value and are concerned about protecting their privacy online. This Privacy Policy explains what information we collect, how we may use that information, with whom that information may be shared, and choices about such uses and disclosures.

Above Average provides this Privacy Policy to help visitors make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the Above Average websites. Visitors remain subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy by using and/or providing information on any Above Average websites.

How We Collect Personal and Non-Personal Data

Personal Data is personally identifiable information about users, including, but not limited to full name, birth date, e-mail address or mailing address, phone number, demographic information (such as interests, activities, gender, age, etc.), and any other information that can be used to identify or contact visitors.

The only Personal Data we collect through the Above Average websites is the Personal Data that visitors voluntarily provide to Above Average when participating in certain activities on the Above Average websites such as posting comments, subscribing to our newsletters or other mailing lists, or following our social media accounts (i.e. Facebook, Instagram, Pinterest, Tumblr, Twitter, YouTube, etc.).

It may be possible for you to browse certain parts of the Above Average websites without revealing any Personal Data, however, you may lose anonymity once you provide your Personal Data, and by doing so, you agree to the collection, transfer and storage of that information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

Additionally, Above Average may collect other data that does not qualify as Personal Data (“Non-Personal Data“) when visitors visit certain pages on the Above Average websites. Non-Personal Data may include, but is not limited to, how many visitors access the Above Average websites, which web or mobile browsers visitors use, the date and time of their visits, the length of their stays, and which pages they view. Above Average may use technology to automatically collect and track Non-Personal Data. Above Average may also use Google Analytics to collect Non-Personal Data about the use of the Above Average websites such as website traffic by age, gender, affinity, and other categories.

Child Privacy (Children under the Age of 13)

Under the Children’sOnline Privacy and Protection Act (“COPPA“), general audience website operators are required to obtain prior parental consent if they knowingly collect, use or disclose any Personal Data from a child under the age of 13.

Here at Above Average, our websites are not directed to or intended to be used by children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect, use, or disclose any Personal or Non Personal Data from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as soon as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under the age of 13, please contact us at [legal@aboveaverage.com](mailto:legal@aboveaverage.com).

Note to International Users

If you are visiting any Above Average website from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States. The data protection laws of the United States might not be as comprehensive as those in your country; however, we will take all necessary and reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy is protected.

How We Use, Protect, and Disclose Your Personal and Non-Personal Data

Above Average may use Personal and/or Non-Personal Data for a variety of reasons, including but not limited to contacting visitors, sending weekly newsletters, notifying visitors about upcoming events, understanding our visitors and markets,improving and/or assessing general visitor interest in various products and services, offering visitors additional products or services, compiling statistics about users and their use of our websites, improving the content and functionality of Above Average websites, and/or requesting feedback on the Above Average websites.

Above Average uses physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to protect your Personal Data against unauthorized access, however, we cannot guarantee that your Personal Data will never be compromised. If Above Average learns of a security systems breach, we will attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps.

From time to time, the Above Average websites may contain hyperlinks to third-party websites that are not operated by Above Average. Above Average does not control nor endorse any activities of these websites and is not responsible for their data practices. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any website that you visit before using the website or providing any Personal Data.

Additionally, Above Average may disclose Personal and/or Non-Personal Data to third parties if (a) you have authorized the disclosure, (b) if we reasonable believe in good faith that is appropriate to do so (e.g., to take precautions against liability, investigate and defend against any third-party claims or allegations, protect the security or integrity of our websites, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Above Average, our visitors or others), or (c) when it is reasonably necessary (e.g., if required or authorized to do so by state and federal laws, or in response to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant).

We may also share Personal and/or Non-Personal Data with our parent company, subsidiaries, successors, assigns, affiliates and other related third parties who may use such Personal and/or Non-Personal Data. If we share your Personal and/or Non-Personal Data with third parties, we require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with this Privacy Policy, use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information, and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

Cookies, Web Beacons, and Log File Information

During your visit to an Above Average website and or included in any Above Average correspondence, we may store and/or send one or more of the following types of technologies that uniquely identifies your browser. The information we obtain from these technologies enables us to customize and measure the overall effectiveness of our websites.

Cookies: A cookie is a piece of data – a small text file – stored on a visitor’s Internet-equipped device that provides information about the visitor. Cookies are used as a convenience feature, but can be disabled, removed, or blocked using the browser settings. Some features of the Above Average websites may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

Web Beacons or Clear GIFs: Used to track the online usage patterns of our visitors anonymously (e.g., Non-Personal Data) and/or to track which emails are opened by recipients.

Log File Information: Automatically recorded Non-Personal Data that your web browser sends whenever a visitor visits any website, which may include the amount of time spent on particular pages, and/or the date and time of request; browser type and browser language; domain names; Internet Protocol (“IP”) address; number of clicks to track marketing campaigns, administer the site, track user movement, and/or gather broad demographic information for aggregate use; pages viewed and the order of those pages; referring / exit pages and URLs; and other web requests.

From time to time, our partners or affiliates may use cookies on our site. Above Average has no control over these cookies. This Privacy Policy only covers the use of cookies by Above Average and does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties.

Third Party Advertising and Do Not Track

We will not share your Personal Data with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent, and/or without providing you with the ability to opt-out. However, we may use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes.

If at any time you wish to opt-out, you can let us know by following the “unsubscribe” link found in every Above Average email, or by contacting us at [legal@aboveaverage.com](mailto:legal@aboveaverage.com). To learn more about behavioral advertising or to opt-out of this type of advertising, visit networkadvertising.org.

Digital Millennium Copyright Act

If you believe that content published on an Above Average website infringes your intellectual property rights, please notify Above Average of your claim in accordance with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act and the procedure set forth below.

A notification of claimed copyright infringement should be emailed to [legal@aboveaverage.com](mailto:legal@aboveaverage.com), Subject line: “Above Average DMCA Takedown Request”, and include the following information:

  1. Your address, telephone number and email address;
  2. A description of the copyrighted work or other intellectual property that you claim has been infringed;
  3. A description of the material that you claim is infringing and where it is located on the Above Average Website, including the page address;
  4. A statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright or intellectual property owner, its agent, or the law;
  5. A statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in your notice is accurate and that you are the copyright or intellectual property owner or authorized to act on the copyright or intellectual property owner’s behalf; and
  6. A physical or electronic signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright or other intellectual property interest.

Keep in mind that if you knowingly make a false claim in a DMCA takedown notice, you could be subject to liability for damages, court costs and attorneys’ fees under federal law.

Questions About Our Privacy Policy

Above Average reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy. Any such changes will be included on this page. We encourage you to check this page periodically.

This Privacy Policy is in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act; if you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to [legal@aboveaverage.com](mailto:legal@aboveaverage.com).

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [legal@aboveaverage.com](mailto:legal@aboveaverage.com)

Effective Date: 9/1/2014
